A Guide to the The Photographic Archive of Fairfax County, Virginia - The Slide Collection, 1961-1998
Virginia Room, Fairfax County Public Library
- Havener House, Centerville, 1966 August; Box 4: HAVE-3 (2 of 5)
- Havener House, Centerville, 1966 August; Box 4: HAVE-3 (3 of 5)
- Havener House, Centerville, 1966 August; Box 4: HAVE-3 (4 of 5)
- Havener House, Centerville, 1966 August; Box 4: HAVE-3 (5 of 5)
- Hayfield, 1968; Box 4: HAYF-1
- Hayfield, 1968; Box 4: HAYF-2
- Hayfield, 1968; Box 4: HAYF-3
- Hayfield, 1968; Box 4: HAYF-4
- Hayfield, 1968; Box 4: HAYF-5
- Hayfield, 1968; Box 4: HAYF-6
- Hayfield, 1968; Box 4: HAYF-7
- Hayfield, 1968; Box 4: HAYF 8
- Herndon, Unidentified Stone House, 1968 May; Box 4: HERN-1
- Herndon, Unidentified Stone House, 1968 May; Box 4: HERN-2
- Herndon, Unidentified Stone House, 1968 May; Box 4: HERN-3
- Herndon, Unidentified Stone House, 1968 May; Box 4: HERN-4
- Herndon, Unidentified Stone House, 1968 May; Box 4: HERN-5
- Herndon, Unidentified House, 1968 May; Box 4: HERN-6
- Herndon, Guth House, 630 Oak St., 1968; Box 4: HERN-GUTH-1
- Herndon, Guth House, 630 Oak St., 1968; Box 4: HERN-GUTH-2 (1 of 2)
- Herndon, Guth House, 630 Oak St., 1968; Box 4: HERN-GUTH-2 (2 of 2)
- Herndon Railroad Station, 1968; Box 4: HERN-RR-2
- Herndon Railroad Station, 1968; Box 4: HERN-RR-3
- Herndon Railroad Station, 1968; Box 4: HERN-RR-4
- Hitaffer Road (photo by E. Breitenbach), 1966; Box 4: HITA-1
- Hitaffer Road (photo by E. Breitenbach), 1966; Box 4: HITA-1
- Holly Knoll, Dranesville (photo by E. Breitenbach), 1966; Box 4: HOKN-1 (1 of 3)
- Holly Knoll, Dranesville (photo by E. Breitenbach), 1966; Box 4: HOKN-1 (2 of 3)
- Holly Knoll, Dranesville (photo by E. Breitenbach), 1966; Box 4: HOKN-1 (3 of 3)
- Hope Park (photo by Nan Netherton), 1973 April; Box 4: HOPE-1 (1 of 4)
- Hope Park (photo by Nan Netherton), 1973 April; Box 4: HOPE-1 (2 of 4)
- Hope Park, 1973; Box 4: HOPE-1 (3 of 4)
- Hope Park, 1973; Box 4: HOPE-1 (4 of 4)
- Hope Park, Outbuilding, 1966; Box 4: HOPE-2 (1 of 3)
- Hope Park, Outbuilding, 1966; Box 4: HOPE-2 (2 of 3)
- Hope Park, Garden House (photo by Nan Netherton), 1973; Box 4: HOPE-2 (3 of 3)
- Hope Park Mill, Mill Race in 1938, Popes Head Road, 1974; Box 4: HOPE-4 (1 of 2)
- Hope Park Mill, Mill Race in 1938, Popes Head Road, Undated; Box 4: HOPE-4 (2 of 2)
- Hope Park Lane, 1973; Box 4: HOPE-5 (1 of 3)
- Hope Park Lane, 1973; Box 4: HOPE-5 (2 of 3)
- Hope Park Lane (photo by Nan Netherton), 1973; Box 4: HOPE-5 (3 of 3)
- Hope Park, Cedar Rows, South Side, Popes Head Road (photo by Nan Netherton), 1973; Box 4: HOPE-6 (1 of 2)
- Hope Park, Cedar Rows, South Side, Popes Head Road (photo by Nan Netherton), 1973; Box 4: HOPE-6 (2 of 2)
- Hospital Dedication Ceremony with Supervisor Martha Pennino, Undated; Box 4: HOSP-1
- Hospital Dedication Ceremony with Supervisor Martha Pennino, Undated; Box 4: HOSP-2
- Huntington, House near Lorton (photo by T. Treacy), 1980 December; Box 4: HUNT-1
- Hunter House, Vienna, Nottoway Park, 1977; Box 4: HUNTER-1
- Huntley, Undated; Box 4: HUNTL-1
- Huntley, Front façade (photo by S. Melville), 1976; Box 4: HUNTL-2
- Huntley, Front, Undated; Box 4: HUNTL-3
- Huntley, Rear façade (photo by S. Melville), 1976; Box 4: HUNTL-4
- Huntley, Necessary (photo by S. Melville), 1976; Box 4: HUNTL-5
- Huntley, Necessary (photo by S. Melville), 1976; Box 4: HUNTL-6
- Huntley, Rear façade (photo by S. Melville), 1976; Box 4: HUNTL-7
- Huntley Meadows Park viewed from Huntley (photo by FCPA), 1976; Box 4: HUNTL-8
- Huntley (photo by William Edmund Barrett), 1969; Box 4: HUNTL-9
- Huntley Meadows Park, aerial, 1990; Box 4: HUNTL-10
- Hurricane David, Damage at 7711 Northdown Road Alexandria, 1979 September 5; Box 4: HURR-D-1
- Hurricane David, Damage at 7711 Northdown Road Alexandria, 1979 September 5; Box 4: HURR-D-2
- Hurricane David, Damage at 7711 Northdown Road Alexandria, 1979 September 5; Box 4: HURR-D-3
- Hurricane David, Damage at 7711 Northdown Road Alexandria, 1979 September 5; Box 4: HURR-D-4
- Hurricane David, Damage, Williamsburg Square, Fairfax (photo by Martin Mooney), 1979 September 5; Box 4: HURR-D-5
- Hurricane David, Damage, Williamsburg Square, Fairfax (photo by Martin Mooney), 1979 September 5; Box 4: HURR-D-6
- Hurricane David, Damage, Williamsburg Square, Fairfax (photo by Martin Mooney), 1979 September 5; Box 4: HURR-D-7
- Hurricane David, Damage, Williamsburg Square, Fairfax (photo by Martin Mooney), 1979 September 5; Box 4: HURR-D-8
- Hurricane David, Damage, Williamsburg Square, Fairfax (photo by Martin Mooney), 1979 September 5; Box 4: HURR-D-9
- Hurricane David, Damage, Williamsburg Square, Fairfax (photo by Martin Mooney), 1979 September 5; Box 4: HURR-D-10
- Hurricane David, Damage, Williamsburg Square, Fairfax (photo by Martin Mooney), 1979 September 5; Box 4: HURR-D-11
- Hurricane David, Damage, Williamsburg Square, Fairfax (photo by Martin Mooney), 1979 September 5; Box 4: HURR-D-12
- Hurricane David, Damage, Williamsburg Square, Fairfax (photo by Martin Mooney), 1979 September 5; Box 4: HURR-D-13
- Hurricane David, Damage, Williamsburg Square, Fairfax (photo by Martin Mooney), 1979 September 5; Box 4: HURR-D-14
- Hurricane David, Damage, Williamsburg Square, Fairfax (photo by Martin Mooney), 1979 September 5; Box 4: HURR-D-15
- Hurricane David, Damage, Williamsburg Square, Fairfax (photo by Martin Mooney), 1979 September 5; Box 4: HURR-D-16
- Hurricane David, Damage (photo by Martin Mooney), 1979 September 5; Box 4: HURR-D-17
- Hurricane David, Damage (photo by Martin Mooney), 1979 September 5; Box 4: HURR-D-18
- Hurricane David, Damage (photo by Martin Mooney), 1979 September 5; Box 4: HURR-D-19
- Hurricane David, Damage (photo by Martin Mooney), 1979 September 5; Box 4: HURR-D-20
- Hurricane David, Damage (photo by Martin Mooney), 1979 September 5; Box 4: HURR-D-21
- Hurricane David, Damage (photo by Martin Mooney), 1979 September 5; Box 4: HURR-D-22
- Hurricane David, Damage (photo by Martin Mooney), 1979 September 5; Box 4: HURR-D-23
- Hurricane David, Damage (photo by Martin Mooney), 1979 September 5; Box 4: HURR-D-24
- Native American engravings, Undated; Box 4: INDI-1
- Native American engravings, 1980; Box 4: INDI-2
- Native American engravings, Undated; Box 4: INDI-3
- Native American engravings, 1979; Box 4: INDI-4
- Native American engravings (John White drawings), 1979; Box 4: INDI-5
- Native American engravings, 1979; Box 4: INDI-6
- Native American engravings, 1988; Box 4: INDI-7
- Ivy Chimney, Dranesville, aerial view, 1968; Box 4: IVYC-1
- Ivy Chimney, Dranesville, 1968; Box 4: IVYC-2
- Ivy Chimney, Dranesville, 1968; Box 4: IVYC-3
- Ivy Chimney, Dranesville (photo by E. Breitenbach), 1966; Box 4: IVYC-4 (1 of 3)
- Ivy Chimney, Dranesville (photo by E. Breitenbach), 1966; Box 4: IVYC-4 (2 of 3)
- Ivy Chimney, Dranesville (photo by E. Breitenbach), 1966; Box 4: IVYC-4 (3 of 3)
- Jackson House (photo by E. Breitenbach), 1966; Box 4: JACK-1 (1 of 3)
- Jackson House (photo by E. Breitenbach), 1966; Box 4: JACK-1 (2 of 3)
- Jackson House (photo by E. Breitenbach), 1966; Box 4: JACK-1 (3 of 3)
- Jackson House, Tombstone (photo by E. Breitenbach), 1966; Box 4: JACK-2 (1 of 3)
- Jackson House, Tombstone (photo by E. Breitenbach), 1966; Box 4: JACK-2 (2 of 3)
- Jackson House, Tombstone (photo by E. Breitenbach), 1966; Box 4: JACK-2 (3 of 3)
- Jerusalem Baptist Church (photo by E. Breitenbach), Undated; Box 4: JERU-1 (1 of 3)
- Jerusalem Baptist Church (photo by E. Breitenbach), Undated; Box 4: JERU-1 (2 of 3)
- Jerusalem Baptist Church (photo by E. Breitenbach), Undated; Box 4: JERU-1 (3 of 3)
- Kelsey Cabin, 1968; Box 4: KELS-1
- Kelsey Cabin, 1968; Box 4: KELS-2
- Kelsey Cabin, 1968; Box 4: KELS-3
- Kelsey Cabin, 1968; Box 4: KELS-4
- Kelsey Cabin, 1968; Box 4: KELS-5
- Kelsey Cabin, 1968; Box 4: KELS-6
- Kelsey Cabin, 1968; Box 4: KELS-7
- Kelsey Cabin, 1968; Box 4: KELS-8
- La Grange, 1968; Box 4: LAGR-1
- La Grange, 1968; Box 4: LAGR-2
- La Grange, 1968; Box 4: LAGR-3
- La Grange, 1968; Box 4: LAGR-4
- La Grange, Snuff stone, 1968; Box 4: LAGR-5
- La Grange, 1968; Box 4: LAGR-6
- La Grange, Tombstone, "Rebecca Kirby, wife of James S. Marder", 1968; Box 4: LAGR-7 (1 of 2)
- La Grange, Tombstone, "Rebecca Kirby, wife of James S. Marder", 1968; Box 4: LAGR-7 (2 of 2)
- Richard Lahey House, sketch, 1972; Box 4: LATHE-1 (1 of 3)
- Richard Lahey House, sketch, 1972; Box 4: LATHE-1 (2 of 3)
- Richard Lahey House, sketch, 1972; Box 4: LATHE-1 (3 of 3)
- Langley Friends Meeting House (photo by Nan Netherton), 1973; Box 4: LANG-FMH-1 (1 of 2)
- Langley Friends Meeting House (photo by Nan Netherton), 1973; Box 4: LANG-FMH-1 (2 of 2)
- Langley Friends Meeting House, 1968; Box 4: LANG-FMH-2
- Langley Friends Meeting House, 1968; Box 4: LANG-FMH-3
- Langley Friends Meeting House, 1968; Box 4: LANG-FMH-4
- Langley Friends Meeting House, 1968; Box 4: LANG-FMH-5
- Langley Friends Meeting House, 1968; Box 4: LANG-FMH-6
- Langley Friends Meeting House, 1968; Box 4: LANG-FMH-7
- Lebanon, 1971; Box 4: LEBA-1 (1 of 2)
- Lebanon, 1971; Box 4: LEBA-1 (2 of 2)
- Lebanon, 1971; Box 4: LEBA-2 (1 of 2)
- Lebanon, 1971; Box 4: LEBA-2 (2 of 2)
- Lebanon, 1971; Box 4: LEBA-3
- Lebanon, 1971; Box 4: LEBA-4
- Lebanon, 1971; Box 4: LEBA-5 (1 of 2)
- Lebanon, 1971; Box 4: LEBA-5 (2 of 2)
- Lebanon, 1971; Box 4: LEBA-6
- Lebanon, 1971; Box 4: LEBA-7 (1 of 2)
- Lebanon, 1971; Box 4: LEBA-7 (2 of 2)
- Lebanon, 1971; Box 4: LEBA-8 (1 of 2)
- Lebanon, 1971; Box 4: LEBA-8 (2 of 2)
- Lebanon, 1971; Box 4: LEBA-9
- Lebanon, 1971; Box 4: LEBA-10 (1 of 2)
- Lebanon, 1971; Box 4: LEBA-10 (2 of 2)
- Lebanon, 1971; Box 4: LEBA-11
- Lebanon, 1971; Box 4: LEBA-12
- Lebanon, 1971; Box 4: LEBA-13
- Lebanon, 1971; Box 4: LEBA-14 (1 of 3)
- Lebanon, 1971; Box 4: LEBA-14 (2 of 3)
- Lebanon, 1971; Box 4: LEBA-14 (3 of 3)
- Lebanon, Painted ceiling, 1971; Box 4: LEBA-15
- Lebanon, Painted ceiling, 1971; Box 4: LEBA-16
- Lebanon, Painted ceiling, 1971; Box 4: LEBA-17 (1 of 2)
- Lebanon, Painted ceiling, 1971; Box 4: LEBA-17 (2 of 2)
- Lebanon, Painted ceiling, 1971; Box 4: LEBA-18 (1 of 3)
- Lebanon, Painted ceiling, 1971; Box 4: LEBA-18 (2 of 3)
- Lebanon, Painted ceiling, 1971; Box 4: LEBA-18 (3 of 3)
- Lebanon, Painted ceiling, 1971; Box 4: LEBA-19 (1 of 2)
- Lebanon, Painted ceiling, 1971; Box 4: LEBA-19 (2 of 2)
- Lebanon, 1971; Box 4: LEBA-20
- Lebanon, 1971; Box 4: LEBA-21
- Lebanon, Interior of barn, 1971; Box 4: LEBA-22
- Lebanon, Interior of barn, 1971; Box 4: LEBA-23
- Lebanon, Interior of barn, 1971; Box 4: LEBA-24
- Lebanon, 1971; Box 4: LEBA-25
- Lebanon, Painted ceiling, 1971; Box 4: LEBA-26 (1 of 2)
- Lebanon, Painted ceiling, 1971; Box 4: LEBA-26 (2 of 2)
- Leeton, 1968; Box 4: LEET-1 (1 of 2)
- Leeton, 1968; Box 4: LEET-1 (2 of 2)
- Leeton, Undated; Box 4: LEET-2
- Level Green, Centerville (photo by E. Breitenbach), 1967; Box 4: LEVE-1 (1 of 3)
- Level Green, Centerville (photo by E. Breitenbach), 1967; Box 4: LEVE-1 (2 of 3)
- Level Green, Centerville (photo by E. Breitenbach), 1967; Box 4: LEVE-1 (2 of 3)
- Level Green, Centerville (photo by E. Breitenbach), 1967; Box 4: LEVE-2 (1 of 3)
- Level Green, Centerville (photo by E. Breitenbach), 1967; Box 4: LEVE-2 (2 of 3)
- Level Green, Centerville (photo by E. Breitenbach), 1967; Box 4: LEVE-2 (3 of 3)
- Marie Butler Leven Preserve (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), 1971; Box 4: LEVE-PR-1
- Marie Butler Leven Preserve (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), 1971; Box 4: LEVE-PR-2
- Marie Butler Leven Preserve (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), 1971; Box 4: LEVE-PR-3
- Marie Butler Leven Preserve (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), 1971; Box 4: LEVE-PR-4
- Marie Butler Leven Preserve (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), 1971; Box 4: LEVE-PR-5
- Marie Butler Leven Preserve (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), 1971; Box 4: LEVE-PR-6
- Marie Butler Leven Preserve (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), 1971; Box 4: LEVE-PR-7
- Marie Butler Leven Preserve (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), 1971; Box 4: LEVE-PR-8
- Marie Butler Leven Preserve (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), 1971; Box 4: LEVE-PR-9
- Marie Butler Leven Preserve (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), 1971; Box 4: LEVE-PR-10
- Marie Butler Leven Preserve (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), 1971; Box 4: LEVE-PR-11
- Marie Butler Leven Preserve (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), 1971; Box 4: LEVE-PR-12
- Marie Butler Leven Preserve (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), 1971; Box 4: LEVE-PR-13
- Marie Butler Leven Preserve (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), 1971; Box 4: LEVE-PR-14
- Marie Butler Leven Preserve (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), 1971; Box 4: LEVE-PR-15
- Marie Butler Leven Preserve (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), 1971; Box 4: LEVE-PR-16
- Marie Butler Leven Preserve (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), 1971; Box 4: LEVE-PR-17
- Marie Butler Leven Preserve (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), 1971; Box 4: LEVE-PR-18
- Maplewood (photo by E. Breitenbach), 1967; Box 5: MAPL-1
- Maplewood (photo by E. Breitenbach), 1967; Box 5: MAPL-2
- Maplewood, 1968; Box 5: MAPL-3
- Maplewood, 1968; Box 5: MAPL-4
- Maplewood, 1968; Box 5: MAPL-5
- Maplewood, 1968; Box 5: MAPL-6
- Maplewood, 1968; Box 5: MAPL-7
- Maplewood, 1968; Box 5: MAPL-8
- Maplewood, 1968; Box 5: MAPL-9
- Maplewood, 1968; Box 5: MAPL-10
- Maplewood, 1968; Box 5: MAPL-11
- Maplewood (photo by E. Breitenbach), 1967; Box 5: MAPL-12
- Maplewood (photo by E. Breitenbach), 1967; Box 5: MAPL-13
- Maplewood (photo by E. Breitenbach), 1967; Box 5: MAPL-14
- Site of Maplewood (photo by Nan Netherton), 1973; Box 5: MAPL-15
- Map of the United States, Public Record Office-Crown c.1720, Undated; Box 5: MAPS-UNS-1
- Map of Virginia-Maryland, Public Record Office-Crown c.1681, Undated; Box 5: MAPS-VAMD-1
- Marshall House, Burke (photo by FCPA), 1975; Box 5: MARS-1
- Marshall Cemetery, Burke, 1998; Box 5: MARS-2
- Marshall Cemetery, Burke, 1998; Box 5: MARS-3
- Massey Building, Aerial, 1970 February; Box 5: MASS-B-2
- Little White House, 10530 Page Avenue, Fairfax (Occupied variously by Fairfax County Community Services Board, Human Rights Office, EEO Division of Personnel, and Volunteer Action Center), 1983; Box 5: MASS-B-3
- Little White House, 10530 Page Avenue, Fairfax, 1983; Box 5: MASS-B-4
- Little White House, 10530 Page Avenue, Fairfax, 1983; Box 5: MASS-B-5
- Little White House, 10530 Page Avenue, Fairfax, 1983; Box 5: MASS-B-6
- Little White House, 10530 Page Avenue, Fairfax, 1983; Box 5: MASS-B-7
- Mason House, 1968; Box 5: MASO-H-1
- Mason House, 1968; Box 5: MASO-H-2
- Mason House, 1968; Box 5: MASO-H-3
- Mason House, 1968; Box 5: MASO-H-4
- Mayfield, Dranesville, 1968; Box 5: MAYF-1
- Mayfield, Dranesville, 1968; Box 5: MAYF-2
- Mayfield, Dranesville, 1968; Box 5: MAYF-3
- Mayfield, Dranesville (photo by E. Breitenbach), 1967; Box 5: MAYF-4
- Mayfield, Dranesville (photo by E. Breitenbach), 1967; Box 5: MAYF-5
- Mayfield, Dranesville (photo by E. Breitenbach), 1967; Box 5: MAYF-6
- Unidentified farm in McLean, Undated; Box 5: MCLE-1
- Melpar (photo by Richard Sakatoto), 1977; Box 5: MEL-1
- Merry Hill, McLean (photo by E. Breitenbach), 1967; Box 5: MERR-H-1
- Merry Hill, McLean (photo by E. Breitenbach), 1967; Box 5: MERR-H-2
- Merry Hill, McLean (photo by E. Breitenbach), 1967; Box 5: MERR-H-3
- Metro, Construction Aerial Survey (WMATA photo by Paul Myatt), 1988; Box 5: METRO-1
- Metro, Edmund Jonson cleaning Metro Center Station pylon (WMATA photo by Larry Levine), 1985 August 12; Box 5: METRO-2
- Metro, Ballston aerial (WMATA photo by Paul Myatt), Undated; Box 5: METRO-3
- Metro, Clarendon aerial (WMATA photo by Paul Myatt), 1987; Box 5: METRO-4
- Metro, Silver Spring station (WMATA photo by Larry Levine), 1987; Box 5: METRO-5
- Metro, Silver Spring aerial (WMATA photo by Larry Levine), 1987; Box 5: METRO-6
- Metro, White Flint aerial (WMATA photo by Larry Levine), 1987; Box 5: METRO-7
- Metro, Bethesda aerial (WMATA photo by Larry Levine), 1987; Box 5: METRO-8
- Metro, Rockville Pike aerial (WMATA photo by Larry Levine), 1987; Box 5: METRO-9
- Metro, Far East Trade Center rendering (WMATA photo by Larry Levine), 1987; Box 5: METRO-10
- Metro, Gallery Place aerial (WMATA photo by Larry Levine), 1987; Box 5: METRO-11
- Metro, Construction Aerial Survey (WMATA photo by Phil Portlock), 1988; Box 5: METRO-12
- Metro, Metro Center interior (WMATA photo by Larry Levine), 1987; Box 5: METRO-13
- Metro, Metro Center and Hechts aerial (WMATA photo by Larry Levine), 1987; Box 5: METRO-14
- Metro, Construction Aerial Survey (WMATA photo by Paul Myatt), 1988; Box 5: METRO-15
- Metro, Dupont Circle Construction (WMATA photo by Paul Myatt), 1975 April; Box 5: METRO-16
- Metro, Arlington Cemetery and USA Today Building (WMATA photo by Larry Levine), 1987; Box 5: METRO-17
- Metro, Map of Metro System (WMATA photo by Paul Myatt), 1987; Box 5: METRO-18
- Metro, Metro Logo (WMATA photo by Paul Myatt), 1987; Box 5: METRO-19
- Mitchell-Weeks House, Chantilly (photo by FCPA), 1975; Box 5: MITC-1
- Money-Burton House, East Wing (fireplace and chimney inside), 1977 August; Box 5: MONE-1
- Moorefield (photo by FCPA), 1976; Box 5: MOOR-1
- Mount Air, Wedding with owner E.S. Enochs pictured (photo by Taylor Gregg - donated by Mayo Stuntz), 1971 August; Box 5: MOUN-A-1
- Mount Air, Wedding (photo by Taylor Gregg - donated by Mayo Stuntz), 1971 August; Box 5: MOUN-A-2
- Mount Air, Wedding (photo by Taylor Gregg - donated by Mayo Stuntz), 1971 August; Box 5: MOUN-A-3
- Mt. Gilead, Centreville (photo by E. Breitenbach), 1972; Box 5: MOUN-G-1
- Mt. Gilead, Centreville (photo by E. Breitenbach), 1972; Box 5: MOUN-G-2
- Mount Vernon, View from across the Potomac River, 1968; Box 5: MOUN-VN-1
- Mount Vernon, View from across the Potomac River, 1968; Box 5: MOUN-VN-2
- Mount Vernon, View from across the Potomac River, 1968; Box 5: MOUN-VN-3
- Mount Vernon, View from across the Potomac River, 1968; Box 5: MOUN-VN-4
- Mount Vernon, The Powel Coach, Undated; Box 5: MOUN-VN-7
- Mount Vernon, The Piazza, Undated; Box 5: MOUN-VN-8
- Mount Vernon, Flower garden, Undated; Box 5: MOUN-VN-9
- Mount Vernon, Aerial view, 1980; Box 5: MOUN-VN-10
- Mountain View, Centreville, 1968; Box 5: MOUN-VW-1
- Mountain View, Centreville, 1968; Box 5: MOUN-VW-2
- Mountain View, Centreville, 1968; Box 5: MOUN-VW-3
- Mountain View, Centreville, 1968; Box 5: MOUN-VW-4
- Mountain View, Centreville, 1968; Box 5: MOUN-VW-5
- Mountain View, Centreville, 1968; Box 5: MOUN-VW-6
- Mountain View, Centreville, 1968; Box 5: MOUN-VW-7
- Mountain View, Centreville, 1968; Box 5: MOUN-VW-8
- Mountain View, Centreville, 1968; Box 5: MOUN-VW-9
- Mountain View, Centreville, 1968; Box 5: MOUN-VW-10
- Mountain View, Centreville, 1968; Box 5: MOUN-VW-11
- Murtaugh House, Centreville, 1968; Box 5: MURT-1
- Murtaugh House, Centreville, 1968; Box 5: MURT-2
- Murtaugh House, Centreville, 1968; Box 5: MURT-3
- Murtaugh House, Centreville, 1968; Box 5: MURT-4
- Murtaugh House, Centreville, 1968; Box 5: MURT-5
- Murtaugh House, Centreville, 1968; Box 5: MURT-6
- Murtaugh House, Centreville, 1968; Box 5: MURT-7
- Murtaugh House, Centreville, 1968; Box 5: MURT-8
- Murtaugh House, Centreville, 1968; Box 5: MURT-9
- Murtaugh House, Centreville, 1968; Box 5: MURT-10
- Murtaugh House, Centreville, 1968; Box 5: MURT-11
- Newington Post Office and Pearson's Store, 1968; Box 5: NEW1-PO-1
- Newington Railroad Station, 1968; Box 5: NEW1-RR-1
- Newington Railroad Station, 1968; Box 5: NEW1-RR-2
- Newington Railroad Station, 1968; Box 5: NEW1-RR-3
- Newington Railroad Station, 1968; Box 5: NEW1-RR-4
- Kinchloe Mill, Undated; Box 5: NEWT-M-1
- Kinchloe Mill, Mill wheel, Undated; Box 5: NEWT-M-2
- Northern Virginia Community College (NOVA), Annandale campus, aerial, 1970; Box 5: NVCC-1
- Northern Virginia Community College (NOVA), Annandale campus, 1970; Box 5: NVCC-2
- Oakton Bargain Den, 1970; Box 5: OAKT-1
- Orchard Hill (photo by E. Breitenbach), 1966; Box 5: ORCH-1
- Orchard Hill (photo by E. Breitenbach), 1966; Box 5: ORCH-2
- Orchard Hill (photo by E. Breitenbach), 1966; Box 5: ORCH-3
- Ossian Hall, Burning on September 3, 1959, Undated; Box 5: OSSI-1
- Ossian Hall, Logo of Annandale Volunteer Fire Department (photo by Nan Netherton), Undated; Box 5: OSSI-2 (1 of 2)
- Ossian Hall, Logo of Annandale Volunteer Fire Department (photo by Nan Netherton), Undated; Box 5: OSSI-2 (2 of 2)
- Pfliegger's Meat Bus, Route 7 west of Tyson's Corner, 1966; Box 5: PFLI-1 (1 of 2)
- Pfliegger's Meat Bus, Route 7 west of Tyson's Corner, 1966; Box 5: PFLI-1 (2 of 2)
- Pleasant Grove Methodist Church, 1968; Box 5: PLEA-1
- Pleasant Grove Methodist Church, 1968; Box 5: PLEA-2
- Pleasant Grove Methodist Church, 1968; Box 5: PLEA-3
- Pleasant Grove Methodist Church, 1968; Box 5: PLEA-4
- Pleasant Grove Methodist Church, 1968; Box 5: PLEA-5
- Pleasant Grove Methodist Church, 1968; Box 5: PLEA-6
- Pleasant Grove Methodist Church, 1968; Box 5: PLEA-7
- Pleasant Grove Methodist Church, 1968; Box 5: PLEA-8
- Pohick Bay Regional Park, 1975; Box 5: POHI-B-1 (1 of 2)
- Pohick Bay Regional Park, 1975; Box 5: POHI-B-1 (2 of 2)
- Pohick Bay Regional Park, Undated; Box 5: POHI-B-2
- Pohick Bay Regional Park, Refuge, Undated; Box 5: POHI-B-3
- Pohick Bay Regional Park, Pohick Creek, Undated; Box 5: POHI-B-4
- Pohick Bay Regional Park, Fall season, 1973; Box 5: POHI-B-5
- Pohick Bay Regional Park, 1973; Box 5: POHI-B-6
- Pohick Bay Regional Park, Aerial view of siltation at Mason's Neck Marsh, 1971; Box 5: POHI-B-7
- Pope-Leighey House, Undated; Box 5: POPE-1 (1 of 2)
- Pope-Leighey House, Undated; Box 5: POPE-1 (2 of 2)
- Pope-Leighey House, Undated; Box 5: POPE-2
- Pope-Leighey House, Undated; Box 5: POPE-3
- Bryan Fairfax, 8th Lord Fairfax (1736-1802), 1969; Box 5: PORTRAIT-1
- George William Fairfax (1724-1787), 1969; Box 5: PORTRAIT-2
- Thomas Fairfax, 6th Lord Fairfax (1693-1781), Undated; Box 5: PORTRAIT-3
- Thomas Fairfax, 9th Lord Fairfax (1762-1846), 1969; Box 5: PORTRAIT-4
- Eleanor D. Hertle of Gunston Hall, Undated; Box 5: PORTRAIT-5
- Eleanor D. Hertle of Gunston Hall, Undated; Box 5: PORTRAIT-6
- Louis Hertle of Gunston Hall, Undated; Box 5: PORTRAIT-7
- Louis Hertle of Gunston Hall, Undated; Box 5: PORTRAIT-8
- Sydney Holland, Citizen of the Year, Fairfax County Federation of Civic Associations, Undated; Box 5: PORTRAIT-9
- Michael Johnson, Park Authority, 1991; Box 5: PORTRAIT-10
- Bruce Kravinsky, 1991; Box 5: PORTRAIT-11
- Larry Moore, Park Authority, 1991; Box 5: PORTRAIT-12
- James Muir, Pastor of Presbyterian Meeting House, Alexandria, VA, Undated; Box 5: PORTRAIT-13
- Captain John Smith (1580-1631), Undated; Box 5: PORTRAIT-14
- George Washington, Parson Weem's Fable on Canvas, 1939, Undated; Box 5: PORTRAIT-15
- Quailwood (photo by E. Breitenbach), 1967; Box 5: QUAI-1
- Quailwood (photo by E. Breitenbach), 1967; Box 5: QUAI-2
- Quailwood (photo by E. Breitenbach), 1967; Box 5: QUAI-3
- Ravensworth Stable and Coach House, Undated; Box 5: RAVE-1
- Ravensworth Stable and Coach House, Undated; Box 5: RAVE-2
- Ravensworth Stable and Coach House, Undated; Box 5: RAVE-3
- Ravensworth Stable and Coach House, Undated; Box 5: RAVE-4
- Ravensworth Stable and Coach House, Undated; Box 5: RAVE-5
- Ravensworth Stable and Coach House, Undated; Box 5: RAVE-6
- Ravensworth Stable and Coach House, Undated; Box 5: RAVE-7
- Ravensworth Stable and Coach House, Undated; Box 5: RAVE-8
- Ravensworth Stable and Coach House, Undated; Box 5: RAVE-9
- Reston, Lake Anne Village Center, 1968; Box 5: REST-1
- Reston, Lake Anne Village Center, 1972; Box 5: REST-2
- Reston, Lake Anne Village Center, 1968; Box 5: REST-4
- Reston, Lake Anne Village Center, 1968; Box 5: REST-6
- Reston, Lake Anne Village Center, 1968; Box 5: REST-7
- Reston, Lake Anne Village Center, 1968; Box 5: REST-8
- Reston, Lake Anne Village Center, 1968; Box 5: REST-9
- Reston, Lake Anne Village Center, 1968; Box 5: REST-10
- Reston, Lake Anne Village Center, 1968; Box 5: REST-11
- Reston, Lake Anne Village Center, 1968; Box 5: REST-12